previously on...
前情提要
you put my kids in danger,and then you lied about it.
你不顾我孩子的安危，而且还要说谎
Do you have some kindof problem with alcohol?
你有酗酒问题吗
Lynette asked a loaded question.
Lynette关切地提出了问题
I'm the one who wassleeping with your son,
和你儿子偷情的人是我
but it's over now.
不过现在已经结束了
No,you're wrong. It's noteven close to being over.
不，你错了，离结束还远着呢
Gabrielle confessed...
Gabrielle坦白了事实
here's your mail.
今天的信到了
While noah's search for zach...
而Noah对Zach的找寻...
I worry for that boy.
我很担心那孩子
What kind of people wouldbuy a baby from a junkie?
什么样的人会要吸毒者的孩子啊
Played perfectly into felicia's plot...
完全落入Felicia的掌握之中
see that paul young hasa toy chest of his very own.
确保Paul Young有他自己的玩具箱
For revenge.
因为她要复仇
What made my husband paul young such a good investor
我的丈夫Paul Young之所以 能在投资界出类拔萃
was his uncanny ability to anticipate the future...
完全离不开他那不可思议的预见性
zach,how did youdo this?
Zach，你怎么弄的?
He foresaw the necessity of the velcro shoe.
他提前想到要给孩子穿尼龙刺粘鞋
He predicted the advent of the $3 cup of coffee.
他预言了即食咖啡的到来
He even anticipated the surprising boom in bottled water.
甚至还注意到了瓶装水的吵杂声
Yeah,it's paul young.
是的，我是Paul Young
I've been reading aboutthe election results in brazil.
我在报纸上看到了巴西的选举结果
It's time to buy sugar.
是时候购入蔗糖了
but the crystal ball that served paul so well in the stock market
但这套在股票市场上屡试不爽的办法
sometimes failed him closer to home.
有时在家里并不奏效
- Paul young?
- 是Paul young么
Yeah.
是的
Detective sullivan.
我是Sullivan侦探
You need to come downtownfor questioning.
我们需要你来回答一些问题
About what?
什么问题
We're investigating reportsof credit card fraud,
我们正在调查一启信用卡诈骗案
and your name has been linkedwith several of the victims.
我们发现你和一些受害者有关
Well,it must be some mistake.
肯定是弄错了
Could be.
也许吧
But we still need to go downtownand straighten it out.
不过你还是得跟我走一趟
All right.
好吧
Well...
那...
how longis this gonna take?
要多长时间？
Don't worry about it.It's just a mix-up.
别担心，误会而已
Let's go.
走吧
What's going on?I thought you just wanted to ask me some questions.
怎么回事，不是只问些问题么？
- That's after you're booked.Booked?
- 登记好了就开始
Booked for what?
登记？登记什么？
You can't book himhere anyhow,detective.
这里不能登记，长官
Computers are down.
计算机出故障了
We're all full up.
我们满员了
You gottatake him down to county.
得带他去县里
What is going on?This is crazy.
怎么回事，简直是疯了
I wanna call my lawyer.
我要给律师打电话
What the hell do you guysthink you're doing anyway? Huh?
你们这是在干什么
This is ridiculous.
简直荒谬
I get a phone call!
我要打电话！
Yes,in the world of investments,
没错，在投资界
my husband had a remarkable ability to see the future.
我丈夫的眼光非同一般
Got a message for you,paul young.
有句话要捎给你，Paul Young
Dierdre's fathersaid to give you his regards.
Dierdre的父亲要我给你问声好
But sadly,paul didn't see this one coming at all.
不幸的是，Paul完全没有预料到这些
-------------------------- www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents --------------------------
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Bree van de kamp
Bree Van De Kamp
had a weekly routine she'd been following for years.
多年来都在履行着同一套公事
She cleaned on tuesdays.
周二打扫卫生
She paid her bills on wednesdays.
周三付帐单
She did her laundry on thursdays.
周四洗衣服
And after these daily chores were completed,
这些日常琐事完毕以后
she would reward herself with a little drink.
她总会奖赏自己一杯酒
What bree didn't know  was this latest addition to her routine
可她没有注意到 最近的这一点变化
had been noticed by her friends.
已经引起了她朋友们的注意
And it had now become part of their routine to discuss it.
在一起讨论Bree 就成了她们的日常公事
So apparently bree hada few too many and passed out.
Bree很明显喝多了酒，昏了过去
Next thing I know, I get a call at work--
紧接着，我就在公司接到了电话
someone found my kids wandering the street.
说有人看到我家孩子跑到了大街上
Oh,my god!
天啊
Have you seen bree since?
那你后来有见过Bree吗
No. I'm worried about her,
没有，我很为她担心
but I don't know how I'm gonna get over what she did.
但我实在不知道怎么才能原谅她
hey,bree.
嘿，Bree
How you doing today?
今天感觉怎么样?
I'm really well.
很好
Um,I just saw you all talking before lynette went off to work.
我看到Lynette上班前在跟你们聊天
What were you all talking about?
在聊什么呢
Oh,nothing,really.
哦，没什么
Carlos and I are gonna go see the adoption counselor today.
我和Carlos今天打算去收养所
I'm checking myself into the hospital.
我得去医院
I'm finally gonna get that surgery.
总算要做手术了
Oh. Good for you.
很好
Did lynette mention the little tiff we had?
Lynette提到我和她的那点小干戈了吗?
Just in passing.
一带而过了
She barely mentioned it.
她没说什么
Because what happened was,
因为事实只是...
I accidentally mixed my antihistamine medication with,
我不小心把抗组胺剂混在了酒水里
you know, a little glass of wine I was having, and I-
I fell asleep, you know,while I was...
之后我睡着了，可我当时在...
watching her kids.
照看她的孩子
I mean,I like a little wine with dinner,
我喜欢在用餐时喝一点酒...时不时地
I mean,now and then. You know,who doesn't?
可谁会不喜欢呢?
But,uh,I mean,
可是...
you know, to trash my entire reputation--
在背后说我的坏话就...
oh,bree, she didn't trash you. Honest.
Bree，她没有说你的坏话，真的
Well,good. I mean,I just--
那就好，我...
I really wouldn't want you to get the wrong impression.
我不想让你们产生误会
Well,I'm--I'm going to the mall.
我正要去商场
They're having a white sale today.
他们今天大减价
I think I'm gonna get a new bath mat.
我想去买个浴室防滑垫
Oh,does anyone need one?
要一起去吗?
- No,I'm good.
- 不，没事
Okay,take care.
好的，回见
Wow,did you smell the alcohol on her breath?
她喘一口气都有酒味儿，闻到了吗?
I sure did.
当然
Then our eskimo turns in the camera and says,
然后我们这位爱斯基摩人转向镜头 说到
"polar fresh mints will give your breath
"用南极牌薄荷糖 你的口气也能得个A+"
an 'a'-plus,too."
So what do you think?
怎么样
It feels a little familiar.
感觉似曾相识
Really? I don't think so.
真的？不会吧
No,I'm pretty sure the lowell group used eskimos
不，我肯定Lowell集团已经 用过爱斯基摩人的点子了
in a deodorant commercial they had last month. Remember?
就是他们上个月做的那个除臭剂广告 记得吗
Oh,this is completely different.
这完全不一样
Those were jock eskimos competing in the iditarod.
他们的爱斯基摩人刚刚上大学
Our eskimo's trying to,you know,
我们的爱斯基摩人已经在...
patch things up with his wife.
处理婚姻生活了
Yeah. No,I get the subtle distinction.
恩，我看到了这些小改动
I think we can do better.
我觉得有改善的余地
Okay? So,sally,you're up.
好吗？ 好了，Sally，轮到你了
What do you got for me?
有什么好点子
Hey.
嘿
"I got the subtle distinction"?
"我看到了这些小改动"?
What was that about?
你搞什么
If you really wanna do this now, shut the door.
如果非要现在说，那就关门
Okay,sure, I was a little bitchy.
好吧，我刚才的确有点苛刻了
But you know why? You did a half-ass job in there.
可你知道为什么吗 因为你完全没有全身心投入
Hey,you may not like my idea,
嘿，也许我的创意你不喜欢
but you can't say I didn't work hard.
可也不至于说我没努力吧
Oh,please.
拜托
I live with you.
咱们住在一起
Last night, when you should've been trying to make that pitch work,
昨天晚上你本该在工作
you were watching the game.
可你却在看球赛
I wasn't watching the game.
我才没有
I saw you!
我都看见了
What,okay,now I can't check the score?
我看看比分还不行了？
Are you saying you gave your heart and soul to that eskimo pitch?
你敢说你在爱斯基摩那个项目上尽全力了?
I worked really hard on that pitch.
我已经很卖力了
Did you give it 100%?
可你有100%投入吗
Well,exactly. So? Big deal.
你看吧，有什么大不了的
Go work up some new ideas,
再想些新点子出来
and then we'll go over it during lunch.
我们午饭的时候再讨论
Okay?
好吗
You're the boss.
谁让你是老板呢
Yes,i am.
我的确是啊
Hey.
嘿
Susan.
Susan
Good to see you again.
见到你真高兴
I'm really looking forward to your surgery.
我很期待你的手术
And I'm really hoping you're a lefty.
那我很希望你是左撇子
Nope. I can't even write my name.
不是，我连名字都写不好
But that's what I get for throwing my kid a roller-skating party.
给孩子开一场溜冰派对就是这个下场
Funny. So what about my surgery?
有意思，那我的手术怎么办
Oh,I'll still do it.
哦，我还会做的
With dr. Ron's help,of course.
当然是在Ron医生的协助下
Dr. Cunningham will be standing right beside me.
Cunningham医生会在旁边指导我
With my hands and his brain,
我的手艺，加上他的经验
you got the best parts of both of us.
我俩的长处都被你用上了
Then I'm on board.
那我就放心了
We're keeping you under observation, so,
我们得把你留下来观察
hopefully, we'll operate tomorrow.
希望明天就可以上手术台了
Uh,if you don't mind,
如果不介意的话
I'd like a minute to consult with my patient.
我有些事要和病人单独谈
Oh! Right, your,um,little thing.
哦，对了，那件事
What "little thing"?
什么事?
Um,well,it was--it was gonna be a surprise,but...
本来是想给你一个惊喜 不过...
Oh,my god,
天啊
they're beautiful.
好美啊
Um,look,I've been thinking about us
你看，我仔细考虑过我们俩
a lot lately--
尤其是最近
about putting this operation behind us and where we'll go from there.
想着怎样才能忘掉这次手术 还有我们的今后...
Our future...
我们的未来...
together.
一起的未来
And I really suck at putting my emotions into words, which is,um,
我实在不善于言表
it's why I wrote it all down.
所以我都写了下来
There's a card.
上面有张卡片
Oh.
哦
Uh,but you can't read it.
不过现在不能看
Not--not while I'm here anyway.
我在场的时候绝对不能看
It's way,way too stressful.
实在太困难
Um,I am going to go now.
我得走了
Wow.
哇
Oh,he's so romantic.
他太浪漫了
May I?
能给我看看吗
Oh,it's sort of private.
哦，可这是私人信件
Well,I did help him pick out the flowers.
不过花是我帮他挑的
Oh. Um...
那...
okay.
好吧
There's more on the back.
背面还有
so how does this work?
要做些什么
Do we flip through a catalog or something?
有目录什么的给我们看看吗
I wish it was that easy.
我也希望能那么简单
You have to understand,for every baby,
请你们理解，对于一个孩子来说
there are ten coupleswho want it.
平均有十对家长想要领养
You don't choose your child.The birth mother chooses you.
所以不是你选孩子 而是孩子的生母挑选你们
Really?
是嘛
So what do you thinkour chances are?
那你觉得我们的机会有多大?
We will do anythingthat we need to do.
要我们做什么都可以
Well,your typical birth motheris usually a young girl,
孩子的生母通常都是年轻女性
and she'll just wanna make sureyou're quality people.
她想把孩子托付给可以信赖的家庭
Now to show her that,
为了赢取她的信任
you'll be putting togethera parent portfolio.
就必须表现出你们会尽到家长的职责
What's that?
什么意思?
Family pictures,character references,
像全家福，性格魅力...
that kind of stuff.
诸如此类
So,um,we're auditioningto be parents?
也就是要面试我们咯?
I guessyou could say that.
可以这么说
So just to be clear,
那么简单地说
some slutty cheerleader getsknocked up by the soccer coach
就因为某个淫荡的啦啦队长 被足球教练搞大了肚子
behind the localgas 'n gulp,and she is going to make sure we're quality people?
她就有资格跑来面试我们？
you don't needto answer that.
这个问题不用回答了
You know,you don'thave to hide it from me.
不用左藏右躲的
Hmm?
恩?
Drinking.It doesn't bother me.
我是指酒，我不反对
Oh,I wasn'thiding anything.
哦，我这不是藏着
I was simply...
我只是在...
enjoying the day.
享受时光
What you want?
什么事
Well,um,masonwas my ride to school.
我一直坐Mason的车去上学
And his dad'smoving them to tucson so...
不过他跟着他爸搬到了Tucson 所以...
oh,well,if you needa ride to school, I'm happy to drive you.
如果你要去学校，我可以送你
No,that's not what I want.I want a car.
我不是这个意思，我想要辆车
Well,then I suggestyou get a job.
那我建议你去工作
Why should I go work my ass offat some fast food place
既然我的钱已经够了 为什么还要到快餐店拚死拚活
when I can already affordwhat I want?
Andrew,we're not touchingyour trust fund.
Andrew，你的信托基金不能动啊
- It's my money.
- 但钱是我的
Not until you're 21.
21岁以前不是
And if I had my way, you wouldn't get your handson it until you're 50.
如果要我决定，你50岁以前 我都不会让你动用一分钱
I mean,we both know you'regonna waste every penny of it.
我们都清楚 钱到了你手上肯定都浪费了
Why are youbeing like this?
你为什么要这样
Because,sweetheart,
因为...亲爱的...
it is my job to teach youabout responsibility,
我有责任让你学会履行职责
setting goals,delayed gratification.
学会确立人生目标，学会先劳后享
What do you knowabout delayed gratification?
你知道什么叫先劳后享?
It's not even noon, yet you're already onyour third glass of wine.
还不到中午，你已经喝了3杯了
You know,on second thought, I won't be driving youto school.
仔细想想，我还是不送你去上学了
The walk will do you good.
走一走对你有好处
Mom,I'm not kidding around.
妈，我没开玩笑
I want my money.
我要钱
The answer is no.
我的回答是‘不’
Well,aren't we a mean old drunk?
还真是个烂醉的老太婆
Whatever that wassupposed to teach me,
不管你这是要教我什么
considerthe lesson learned.
就当我学会了
What are you doing here?
你来这儿干吗
I'm just enjoying the silkysmooth moves of dr. Ron.
我只是看看Ron医生的甜言蜜语
Or should I say,"dr. Love"?
或者应该叫他“爱人医生”?
- Give me that. Aah!
- 还给我
This is my favorite--
这段我最喜欢
"I can't wait to bein the operating room with you
"我已等不及走进手术室"
"so I cantouch your heart,
"触碰你的心灵"
"because you've alreadytouched mine so deeply."
"因为你已经深深触动了我"
Okay,that part sounds betterwhen you don't read it out loud.
好吧，你不读出来的时候 这段话本来挺好听的
And what are you doingreading it anyway?
而且你读它干吗?
Those are dr. Ron's private thoughts.
那是Ron医生的心里话
Yeah,I got that.
恩，我知道
You know,I sense that he really likes you,susie.
我感觉他的确很喜欢你，Susie
So?
那又怎么样
So do you really like him?
那你喜欢他么?
Of course I do.
当然喜欢
He's smart and funny and kind.
他聪明、风趣、而且善良
Smart,funny,kind.
聪明、风趣、善良
I don't hear the word"love" in there.
我可没听出爱意
Well,that's a big word.
爱是个很庄重的词
We just started dating,and we have a connection,
我们刚开始约会，我们有一种默契
and I'm gonna follow it throughand see where it goes.
我会跟着这种感觉，看看有何发展
Oh,I get it.You're gonna string him along till you feelsomething you don't
我懂了，你会一直拴住他 直到没有感觉为止
and waste the next five yearsof your life.
并为此浪费5年的时间
As opposed to the 12I wasted on you?
相比之下我浪费在你身上的是12年
Why are we talkingabout this?
我们为什么要谈这些
I don't recallasking you your opinion.
我好像从没有问过你的意见
Because we're marriedand I have certain rights,
因为我们是一家人 我享有某些权利
and one of themis the right to badger you.
其中之一就是烦扰你
Okay,you know,you can leave now.
好了，你可以走了
I wish I could M.R.I. Your soul--
我真希望能透视你的灵魂
out!
出去
it's not funny.
这不好玩
hey,watch out for my wife.She's on a tear.
嘿，当心我老婆，她在火头上呢
Oh,here's one we tookon vacation.
这张是我们在度假
Hmm. Gaby,these pictureshave to be wholesome.
Gaby，我们得选那些健康向上的照片
They gotta say...
必须让他们觉得...
"these people will doa great job raising a child."
"这家人能把我的孩子抚养好"
So?
那怎么了？
So you're topless.
可你没穿上衣
Yeah,but it's st. Barts,
没错，可那毕竟是裸体海滩啊
and your hands are coveringmy naughty parts.
而且你的手还遮住了我的重要部位
Do you mean the handthat's holding the tequila shot,
你是指拿着龙舌兰酒那支？
or the one that's holdingthe cuban cigar?
还是握着古巴雪茄那支?
Yeah,that was a good trip.
那真是次难忘的旅行
Gaby!
- Fine. We won't use it.
- 好吧，不选这张
We can't use any of 'em.
哪张都不能选
Every single pictureof the two of us,
这里面每一张照片
we're either drinkingor smoking or naked.
要么就是在抽烟喝酒 要么就是在暴露
So we like to have fun. I mean,who doesn't understand that
我们不过是有点贪玩
better than an unwed,knocked-up teenager?
那些未婚的年轻妈妈最理解这一点了
This is serious.
这是正经事
If we can't sell ourselvesas good people...
如果不能让人家相信我们是好人...
well,then we'll justhave to find someone who can do it for us.
那就必须找其他人帮忙
So you want me to,uh...
这么说你们是要我...
pitch you as parents?
把你们包装成好家长?
You're in advertising.You can do it.
你是做广告的嘛，肯定能行
Just write usa character reference saying we're greatwith kids.
只要把我们描写得很适合带孩子就行了
Oh,this is for you.
哦，这是送给你的
Oh. Well,you don'thave to bribe me.
哦，没必要贿赂我嘛
We're all friends here.(Chuckles)
大家都是朋友
keeping that in mind,would it also be okay if we wereyour kids' godparents?
既然这样，那说我们是你家孩子 的名义双亲也可以吗
Oh! Uh... I guess.
噢！呃 我想行
Great,and can we take somefake pictures to document it?
太好了 我们能照些照片来记载下这一刻吗？
I don't supposeyou brought a corkscrew?
你恐怕没带开瓶器吧
You didn't have a warrant,and if you don't arrest him,
你没有许可 如果你不抓他
then you gotta tell mewhat he wants.
那你得告诉我他要什么
Hello,mike.
你好 Mike
Felicia,what are you doing here?
Felicia 你在这干嘛？
Oh,I left in such a rush.
噢 我离开的太匆忙了
There was a lot of old businessI forgot to wrap up.
有许多旧事我忘记处理了
Well,it must bepretty important business,
一定是很重要的事情
gets you to moveback in next door to the man you think murdered your sister.
才能让你搬回你觉得 谋杀了你妹妹的男人的隔壁
It's funnyyou should mention paul.
你这么说Paul真是好笑
You know,the police cameand took him away last night.
你知道吗 警察昨晚来把他带走了
The police?
警察？
And from the waythey were manhandling him,
从他们推他的方式
ooh,I don't thinkhe'll be back anytime soon.
我想他不会很快就回来了
(Zach) no,I just wannatalk to him,that's all...
不 我只是想和他说话 就这样
what the hell'sgoing on?
到底发生什么了？
It's noneof your concern,mike.
与你无关 Mike
You listen to me,if anythinghappens to paul young--
你听我说 如果Paul Young发生了什么事
it already happened.
已经发生了
Hours ago.
几个小时之前
He's dead?
他死了？
Like I said,
就像我说的
it's none of your concern.
不是你该过问的事
Maybe you don't get it,noah.You screwed up.
也许你没搞懂我的意思 Noah 你把事情弄糟了
You just killedthe most important person in your grandson's life.
你刚杀死了你孙子生命中最重要的人
Do you think he's gonna haveanything to do with you once he finds out?
你觉得当他发现你做的事后 他还会想和你扯上关系吗？
And believe me,
相信我
I'll make sure he finds out.
我保证他会发现的
So,honey,the meat loaf--it's,um,it's a little burnt.
哦 甜心 这个肉馅糕- 它有点烧糊了
Oh,right,I was talkingto susan on the phone,
噢 当时我正和Susan讲电话
and I left it in a little longerthan I should've. Sorry.
我把它放锅里时间长些了 对不起
It's okay. (Sighs)
没事
is it that bad?
有那么糟吗？
No. No,not bad at all.
不 不 一点都不
Oh,good.
恩 好
Parker,don't put your elbowson the table. Come on.
Parker别把你的胳膊放在桌上 快点
But you'd agreeit wasn't your best effort.
不过你答应你不会全力放在工作上的
Huh?
什么？
The meal,the taskyou agreed to take on.
做饭 你答应负责的任务
You'd agree thatyou didn't give it 100%,right?
你答应不会全心放在上面 对吧？
Tom,if you're gonnamake a point,
Tom 如果你想说什么
why don't you do it nowbefore I hurl the plate at you?
最好现在就在说出来 别等我拿盘扔你
Nobody gives 100% of his effortall the time because they can'T.
没人能一直全心投入 因为他们不可能做不到
It is impossible.
那是不可能的
You do the best you can withthe time and energy you have.
在你时间和精力有限的情况下 只需做到最好
Stop right there.This is meat loaf. (Chuckles)
别说了 这只是肉馅糕
your presentationwas business.
你说的是生意
You're saying the clientdeserves more effort than your own family?
你是说客户比你自己的家人 还值得你放更多精力？
Okay.
好
So if I apologizefor upsetting you at work,
如果我为工作时让你难堪了而向你道歉的话
can we get past itand enjoy our meal?
我们能不说这个了 继续吃饭吗？
Absolutely.
当然
I'm sorry.I'm sorry. I am sorry.
对不起 对不起 对不起
Thanks.
谢谢
So,boys,how do you enjoy the meat loaf?
孩子们 肉馅糕怎么样？
It's a little salty.
有点咸
(Preston) yeah.
嗯
Just eat it.
吃吧
there.
好了
Perfect.
完美
All right.
好了
all right,one more time.
好了 再来一次
What?
什么?
Yeah.
对
Dude,I don't wannamess up your face.
老兄 我可不想打破你的脸
Do you love me?
你爱我吗？
Then do what I tell you.
那就照我的话去做
Rough day.
艰难的一天
Yeah.
是阿
I wonder if there's any way thatwe can turn it around still.
我想知道有没什么办法 能使它变好些
Good question.
好问题
But what to do?What to do?
不过 怎么做呢 怎么做呢
Yeah.
对啊
Hi! What's up?
嗨! 怎么了？
Why do you keep trying to do that?
你干吗一直想那么做？
- What?
- 什么?
Trying to get on top.
想到上面去
Of you? No,I'm not.
你上面? 不 我没有
You were pushing on me likeyou were trying to sack me.
你一直推我 就像你要压住我
I felt it.
我感觉到了
Are you serious?
你说真的？
Tom,I wasn't doing anything.I was just going for it.
Tom 我什么也没做 我只是想主动点
I was just lost in the moment.Oh,come on!
我只不过是太投入了 来嘛
Come on,this is silly.I don't wanna argue.
快点 这很傻 我不想争这个
I mean,unless it turns you on.
我的意思是 除非这样让你兴奋
Does it? 'Cause thenI'm all about it,baby.
兴奋了吗？我现在可正在这样做 宝贝
What--what was that?
什么 这是干嘛？
What--what was what?
什么？什么是什么？
You were bracing.
你支起来了
You were bracing with your leg.
你用脚支起来了
I was tryingto lie on top of you,
我正试着躺到你上面
and you were bracing yourselfagainst the mattress
而你抵住床垫
so you didn'thave to get on your back.
这样你就不用躺着
Try and deny it.Try and deny it. You can'T.
否认阿 否认阿 你做不到
Okay,okay,can I just mention you're talking like a crazy person?
好好 我觉得你现在说话像疯子
You can't give it upfor a second,can you?
你就不能停一下吗?
You always haveto call the shots. Always.
你总是要操控一切 一直都是
Is this aboutme being boss again?
又是关于我当你上司的事吗?
You gotta get over it.
你得克服它
That's exactly my point.
这就是我要说的
Exactly.
一点不差
You are notjust my boss at the office.
你不只在办公室是我的上司
You're my boss everywhere.
在任何地方你都是我的上司
Oh,that's ridiculous.
噢 这太荒谬了
You run the show.
你是主演
You run the show,and I'm along for the ride.
你是主演 而我是凑热闹的
I just pushthe little shopping cart,
我只不过推着小小的购物车
let the woman do all the driving.
让女人开车吧
- Tom...
I'm the caddy husband.
我是你的球童
I carry your clubs.
我拿着你的球杆
I am so sorry you feel that way,
真抱歉你是这种感受
but you cannotput that on me.
但你不能怪我
This is your life.
这是你的生活
You wanna run it?
你想主导它?
Then step on up.
那你就上阿
You wanna drive?
你想开车?
Grab the steering wheel.
那就捉住方向盘阿
I mean-- what elseam I supposed to say?
我是说-我还应该说什么?
I'm gonnacheck on the kids.
我去看看孩子
Time to checkyour blood pressure.
该量你的血压了
Oh,sure.
好的
Oh,that's a little tight.Does it have to be that tight?
噢 有点紧 非得这么紧吗?
- Yes.
- 是的
Oh.
哦
okay. Ow,ow. That's actuallystarting to be painful.
好了 嗷 开始疼了
Really?That surprises me.
真的?真让我吃惊
I just assumedyou were dead inside.
我还以为你内部已经死了
Ow! Ow! What the hellare you doing?
嗷!嗷!你到底在干嘛？
I told myself to stayout of this,but I can'T.
我告诉我自己别缠和进来 但我不能
I know that you're married.
我知道你结婚了
I am not!
我没有!
Really? Hmm,'cause that manthat came to see you yesterday,he saidyou're his wife.
真的？哼 因为昨天来看你的男人说 你是他妻子
Oh! Yeah,oh...
噢！是...
no,no,he just said that'cause we used to be married.
不 不 你这么说是因为我们以前结过婚
It's just a force of habit.
只不过是习惯的原因
Oh,that explainseverything.
哦 这倒解释了一切
Except that I checkedyour insurance forms,and you're still married.
我还检查了你的保险单 你还是已婚
So that makes youa lying,adulterous skank.
你这个说谎通奸的烂货
Oh,no. No,no.No,no,nurse hisel.
不不不 Hisel护士
Ow,ow,ow,ow!Ow,nurse hisel!
嗷嗷嗷嗷 Hisel护士！
Ugh! Nurse--oh!
护士 嗷！
Nurse hisel,I can explain.
Hisel护士 我可以解释
Can you,skank?
你能吗 烂货？
Yes. Okay.
是的
I am married,but it's only because my insurance ran out.
我还是已婚 全是因为我的保险用完了
My ex-husband hasa really good coverage plan,
我的前夫保险完好
so he said thathe would remarry me
他说如果我们再婚
so I couldget my operation.
我就能动手术了
Only I didn'twanna tell dr. Ron
我之所以不没告诉Ron医师
'cause I didn't want himto be an accomplice to fraud.
因为我不想他成为诈保案的从犯
So you're what...
这么说你是在...
protecting him?
保护他？
Yeah. It--yes,I am.
是的 是的
Okay.
好吧
As long as you're nottwo-timing him.
你没欺骗他就好
He feelsso strongly about you.
他对你可是真心的
I know. I read the card.
我知道 留言卡片我也看了
But did you readbetween the lines?
那你看出字里行间的意思了吗？
What do you mean?
什么意思？
Okay,I shouldn't betelling you this,
哦 我本不应该告诉你的
but when we were picking outthe flowers for you,
不过在我们为你选花的时候
he said that he was working upthe courage to say he loves you.
他说他要鼓足勇气对你说那三个字
Really?
真的？
Yes!
是的！
But you haveto act surprised,okay?
到时候你得装作很吃惊的样子
Oh,yeah,I'll be surprised.
哦 我会的
So I guess we have the wholeinsurance thing worked out.
那么保险这事就算过去了？
Oh! Pfft. Don't worryabout that. Please.
哦 别担心了
Who am I to cast stones?
我干吗搬起石头砸自己的脚呢？
I mean,heck...
要知道
I didn't passmy nurse's exam.
我当初根本没通过护士资格考试
They didn't even ask me!
他们压根没问
Andrew,did I hear the bell?
Andrew 是不是有人敲门？
Oh,hello.
哦 你好
I'm samuel bormanis.I'm here to see andrew.
我叫samuel bormanis 我是来见andrew的
Oh,okay.Are you a friend of andrew's?
哦  你是andrew的朋友？
I'm his lawyer.
我是他的律师
His lawyer? Well,why on earthwould andrew need a lawyer?
他的律师？andrew干吗要律师？
Here you go,sam.
你来了 sam
honey,what happened to-- to your face?
宝贝 你的脸怎么了？
I...
我...
you hit me.
是被你打的
Don't you remember?
你不记得了？
For the record,I did not punch my son.
我事先声明 我绝对没有打我儿子
I slapped himwith an open palm.
我只是抽了他一耳光
Yeah,but,mom,the thing is,
是的 可是 妈妈
when you drink,you don't knowyour own strength.
你都喝醉了 就不知道下手有多重了
This is ridiculous.
这太可笑了
Can't you seethis is a performance?
你看不出他是在装的吗？
Mrs. Van de kamp,I've heard enough.
Van de kamp夫人 我不想再听下去了
Clearly,this environment isa highly dysfunctional one.
很明显 这个环境实在太差了
Andrew has retained my services in order to pursuea healthier living situation.
Andrew寻求我的帮助 是为了获得更好的健康的生活环境
And what might that be?
什么生活环境？
I,um,I wanna be emancipated.
我 我要求不再受父母管束
Emancipated?
脱离父母监管？
As an emancipated minor,andrew would be able to live on his own.
作为一个脱离监管的未成年人 andrew将独立生活
He'd still go to school,of course,
当然 他还会继续上学
but he'd be releasedfrom all adult supervision.
但是他将脱离任何成年人的监管
Well,that's the silliest thingI've ever heard of.
这简直愚蠢之至
How wouldhe support himself?
他怎么养活自己？
Well,he'd be in completecontrol of his own finances.
他自己管自己的财务
So that's what this is about--your trust fund?
说了半天 原来是为了你的个人基金的事
Obviously,we'd all prefer not to go to family court,
当然 我们都不愿意看到大家对簿公堂
but with the violenceand your D.U.I. Charge,
不过鉴于你有暴力倾向和酒后驾车的记录
it could get ugly.
就算闹上法庭也不会好看的
Uh,mr. Bormanis,
Bormanis先生
I'll need a little timeto think about this.
我需要时间考虑一下
You have 24 hours.
我给你24小时
boy,it really lookslike we're having a good time.
看上去我们还真开心
I sure hope this works.
这次肯定成了
Well,as long as they don'tmake me play guitar,
只要别让我真去弹吉他
I thinkwe're home free.
肯定没问题
Mr. And mrs. Solis,rhoda can see you now.
Solis夫妇 rhoda要见你们
Wow!
哇！
It looks like you spendlots of time with these kids.
你们和孩子们还真待了很长时间
Oh,we take our rolesas godparents very seriously.
我们很珍惜做名义父母的机会
- Don't we,honey?
- 是嘛 亲爱的
Mm-hmm. Yes.
恩 是啊
Oh,they're precious.What are their names?
他们真可爱 都叫什么名字？
Parker and,uh...
Parker 还有...
porter,uh...
porter,呃...
and,uh...
呃...
well,they're all p'S.It is super cute.
反正都是P开头的 特别可爱
One sec.Do you need me,helen?
等一下 什么事 helen?
Hello,gabrielle.
你好啊 gabrielle
Carlos.
I didn't knowyou were adopting.
我还不知道你们要领养孩子
Preston!
The other one's nameis preston.
还有一个孩子叫preston
helen,you work here?
helen 你在这工作？
You all know each other?
你们认识？
What a small world. It sure is.
－世界真小啊 －是啊
Mrs. Solis hired my sonto do her yard work.
Solis夫人曾雇我儿子打点他们家草坪
And also,she would rape him.
她还差点要和我儿子上床
Okay,first of all,it was statutory,
首先协议符合法律规定
and it happenedso long ago.
其次那是好久以前的事了
Was it? I thinkit was only about a year ago.
是嘛 我记得是大约1年前的事
No,it was a year,
不 是正好1年
because it was right beforeyour husband went to prison on slave labor charges.
就在你丈夫因怂恿他人做苦役的罪名 被收监坐牢之前
Rhoda,if you don't mind,
Rhoda 你不介意的话
I think I'll handlethe solis case myself.
我想亲自过问solis夫妇领养一事
I'd like to make it my top priority.Okay.
我会当作重中之重来办的
Oh,and,um,gabrielle,don't bother trying to contact
呃 gabrielle 你也别费心联系
any other adoption agenciesin the area.
其他领养机构了
I'll make surethey know all about you.
我会让他们都知道你的情况的
I think I haveto break up with dr. Ron.
我觉得我得和Ron医师分手了
What? Why?
什么？为什么？
Because he's a gem.
因为他太好了
And apparentlyhe loves me.
而且他也爱我
I'm sorry.I'm not following.
不好意思 我没听明白
Lynette,he is everything
Lynette 他就是
I could possibly wantin a boyfriend,
我心目中的完美男友
and I just don't knowif I feel that...
我不知道我是否感觉到了那种...
spark.
爱情火花
You know,and I really want to.
我很想有那种感觉
Aw,sweetie.
哦 甜心
And he keeps telling mehow special I am
他一直对我说我是多么的特别
and how muchI mean to him...
我对他十分重要...
how he wants to holdmy beating heart in his hand.
他多想手托我的心
Maybe it's because I just haven'tfelt that thunderbolt yet.
也许是因为我还没感觉到心灵的“雷电”震撼
You know,with mike,it hit me.With karl,it his me.
Mike就击中了我 Karl也是
I didn't have to worryabout how I felt
我无需担心自己的感受如何
becausethe thunderbolt told me.
因为那一击就说明了问题
Yeah,yeah.Gotta love the thunderbolt.
是啊 就是喜欢这种感觉
Do I,though? I mean,I do
我呢？我也喜欢
But I don'ttrust it anymore.
但是我不能信这种感觉
You know,those relationshipsturned out to be disasters.
因为靠这种感觉带来的关系现在都成了灾难
Maybe I shouldstick it out with dr. Ron,
也许我应该继续和Ron医师交往
and I should try heading downa road that's growing and slower
继续走在爱情的道路上
intoa sort of kind of love that would sustain itselffor 50 years. Right?
也许慢慢地会持续50年之久 对吗？
Stability,comfort,endurance--I deserve that.
稳定 安逸 持久 我应该拥有这些
Oh,yes!Of course you do.
哦 是的 当然
Still,you gotta lovethe thunderbolt.
不过的确很喜欢雷击的感觉
That's not helpful.
别说那些没用的
Sorry.
对不起
Ah,this is a sign.
这是个征兆
Will you shut up?
你能不能闭嘴？
We lost a baby,found outwe can't conceive another one,
我们失去了一个孩子 又发现不能生孩子了
and ran into helen rowlandat an adoption agency.
结果又在领养所遇到了helen rowland
God is obviouslytrying to tell us something.
上帝似乎是在要告诉我们什么
Carlos,we're catholics,okay?
Carlos 我们是天主教徒
God is pretty johnny one note on the whole subjectof procreation.
上帝对于如何生育根本没什么好见解嘛！ （指玛利亚圣灵怀胎一事）
Hey,and will you stopwith this defeatist attitude?
请你别一副垂头丧气的样子 好吗？
Okay,do you wanta baby or not?
你到底还想不想要孩子了？
I think it's time that we facedreality--
我觉得我们应该面对现实--
we're bad people,and we probably don'teven deserve to be parents.
我们根本就是坏人 不配为人父母
Well,then who the hell does?
那谁配啊？
I mean,look at all the idiotspopping kids.
你看看现在的年轻人
Okay,they're not any morequalified than we are.
比起我们来 他们也好不到哪去
I don't know.
我也不知道
Look,carlos...
carlos...
it doesn't matterwhat we've done in our past.
我们过去的所作所为并不重要
Being a parentmeans rising to the occasion,
为人父母就是要随时面临并解决难题
and that's exactlywhat we're gonna do when we bring our baby home.
我们有了孩子后更要如此
This is the first time I really felt likeyou wanted to have a baby.
这是我第一次觉得你很想要孩子
(Sighs)well,this is the first time someone told meI couldn't have one.
这是我第一次听人告诉我 我不能有自己的孩子
Okay,so whatare we gonna do?
好吧 我们该怎么办？
I mean,no adoption agencyis gonna touch us now.
现在没有哪个收养机构愿意给我们联系了
There are waysto get babies,carlos.
想要孩子还是有其他办法的 carlos
It just might cost us.
不过花费会不小
I have some contactsin the police department.
我在警局有熟人
I've been making calls,but I can't seem to get a straight answerabout your dad.
我也打了电话问了 不过他们似乎都说不清你爸爸究竟怎么了
I don't understand.How do they just lose somebody?
我不太明白 怎么可能会不知道
They don't,not by accident.
他们偏偏就不知道了
But I don't think what happenedto your dad was an accident.
但是我觉得你爸爸的事绝非偶然
What's thatsupposed to mean?
你什么意思？
zach!
Mrs. Tillman.
Tillman夫人
Hello,zachary.You look terrible.
你好 zachary 你脸色不好啊！
Oh,mr. Delfino.
哦 Delfino先生
Isn't thisjust a picture?
还真像啊
Felicia,why are you here?
Felicia 你来干吗？
Young zacharyand I didn't exactly part on the best of terms.
zachary和我的关系也不是完全决裂了
In fact,when the weather's damp,
其实 每当天阴的时候
I'm still remindedof our last good-bye.
我就想起我们最后一次的道别
But forgive and forget.That's my motto.
不过不计前嫌 心无芥蒂 一向是我做人的原则
Macaroon?
来点杏仁饼干吗？
dad!
爸爸！
You all right?
你没事吧？
now how did you knowI love macaroons?
你怎么知道我喜欢杏仁饼干？
it won't end here,you know.Noah taylor doesn't give up.
事情不会就这么结束的 Noah taylor不会这么轻易地放弃
Look,don't worry about us.We'll be gone by morning.
不用你担心 我们明早就远走高飞了
No,it's too latefor that now.
不 太晚了
I guarantee he's got people watching you.
我敢打赌 他一定派人在监视你们
What is it withyou anyway?
你这么费心图什么？
First,you want me to run.
你先是让我逃命
Now you want us to stick around likesitting ducks for this maniac.
现在你又让我们跟傻子似得等死
Go ahead,run. Noah's gotthe cops in his pocket.
好啊 那你逃吧 Noah收买了警察
What do you think's gonna happenthe first time you try to buy gas
你要是用信用卡买汽油 或者 开新户头的话
with a credit card oropen a new bank account?
你知道会发生什么事吗？
So I'm a dead man.
照你这么说 我死定了
Maybe not.
也不一定
Not if we usewhat leverage we have.
只要我们利用一下zack
No way.
没门
The old man's gonna be dead in a couple of months,maybe less.
老家伙还有不到几个月的寿辰
Let him meet zach,
让他见见zach
- play the doting grandfather--
- 做一回慈爱的祖父
I said forget it.
我说了没门
I'll do it.
我愿意
If it meanshe'll leave us alone,
如果他可以放过我们
I'm readyto be leveraged.
我愿意被利用
Nicholsonwill be coming in in about 15 minuteswith a pitch,
Nicholson15分钟内就会带着广告创意来这里
so let's grab everybody and make surewe're all on the same page.
所以大家最好碰个头了解一下情况
Hang on a second.
等等
What's going on?
怎么了？
I need to say this.
我得说出来
Ah,yeah...
哦...
I have been giving youa lot of grief lately about being the boss.
对你当我的老板 我最近一直很不满
But it's justhard for a guy to feel like
但是你要知道 对于一个男人来说
he's not in chargeof any part of his life.
发现他不再万事为首是多么痛苦的一件事啊
But,honey, it goes back and forth.
但是 亲爱的 这种事是时有时无啊
I know. But it just feelsa little one-sided lately,
我知道 但最近偏向的厉害啊
and sometimesI need to drive the train.
有时候我需要去驾驭
But,look,I know it is my issue.
我也知道是我的问题
It's my issue,
我的问题
and I will step upand deal with it.
我会站出来面对的
Whoa. Hello.
哦
What's going on,huh?
你在干吗？
I'm picking up where we left off.
继续昨晚
Last night.
未尽的事务
Oh,I get it. I get it.
哦 我知道了
Ooh! This is your ideaof driving the train.
哦 这就是你所谓的驾驭啊！
And it's very manlyand really impressive,
的确男人味十足 让人惊叹
but it's really,reallybad timing.
不过现在可不是亲热的时候啊
You can't be serious.
你真会搞笑
Mmm. We're gonna--we're gonna be late.
我们 我们可要迟到了
Yeah,we are goingto be late.
我们可要迟到了
Okay.
好吧
There is nothingmore important than family.
没什么比家庭更重要的了
And I think it's so unfairsome are denied their god-given rightto parent
而且我觉得就因为过去的一些风流韵事
just because of a fewsordid incidents in their past.
就不让你们做父母 实在是有失公允
I may have to exploresome unconventional paths to find your child.
我可能会用一些非常手段 来帮你们找到收养的孩子
I might even have to take actionsome might view as unsavory.
有些行为可能会令人不快
But before I do...
所以在我开始之前...
I need proofthat the two of you are prepared
我得需要你们能证明自己
to facethe challenges ahead.
能面对未来的挑战
$20,000.
2万美元
Is that proof enoughfor you?
够了吗？
Yes,it is.
哦 够了
Nice to meet you,young man.
很高兴见到你 年轻人
I'm not gonna hug you.
我可不会去抱你
I don't careif you are my grandfather.
我才不在乎你是不是我的外公
Ah. That's okay.Hugging's not really my thing.
没关系 反正我也不喜欢抱来抱去的
Mike,could you wait outside?
Mike 出去等一下 好吗
I'd like to be alonewith zachary.
我想单独和zachary聊一回
Not a chance.
想都别想
Just curious...
我只是想问一下
why was it so importantyou see me?
你为什么这么急着要见我？
You're my grandson.
因为你是我外孙啊
My flesh and blood.
我的骨肉啊
Isn't it only natural I'd wanta relationship with you?
我想见你不是天经地义嘛？
What kind of relationshipcan we have when I know you triedto kill my dad?
你想杀我爸爸 这也是天经地义吗？
Surely,you can understand the rage I must feeltowards your father.
你应该能理解我为什么如此怨恨你的父亲
Go ahead. Feel all the rageyou wanna feel.
好啊 你尽管怨恨好了
But if anythinghappens to him,
但是如果他出了什么事
I swear to god you are nevergonna see me again.
我发誓你再也不会见到我
You only met metwo minutes ago,
你才见到我两分钟
and here you are,
没想到
already blackmailing me.
就开始恐吓我了
I couldn't be prouder.
我真是感到无比自豪啊
I'm serious.
我可是说真的
I want you to swear you're notgonna do anything to my dad.
我要你发誓不得伤害我的父亲
Which dad?
哪位父亲啊？
You have two of 'em.
你有两个呢
You knowwho I'm talking about--
你知道我说的是谁
my dad,the man who raised me,
养我的那位
the only manI'm ever gonna care about.
我唯一在意的那一位
So swear.
发誓吧
I swear.
我发誓
Well,now thatthe ground rules have been set,
既然规矩也订好了
who's up for somemeaningless small talk?
谁愿意和我闲聊几句啊？
well,if it isn'tthe plumber.
哦 这不是那位水管工嘛
You here to see susan?
你是来看susan的？
Uh,yeah,I just wanted to talkto her before her operation.
我想在她动手术前和她说几句话
Oh?You're cutting it kinda close.
哦 那你来得可真巧啊
She's just aboutto be wheeled into surgery.
她马上就要进手术室了
You know,she's dating her surgeon.
你知道吗 她在和她的那位外科医生约会
Yeah,she told me.
知道她告诉我了
You met him?
你见过他了？
Yeah.
是的
He's,like,6 years old.
他就像个三岁小孩似的
those for her?
这些是给她的？
Yeah. The floristwas having a sale on lilacs.
是的 花店正好特价销售丁香
Dr. Ron just bought her the biggest bouquet of rosesyou've ever seen.
Ron医师刚刚送给她一簇玫瑰花
It was disgusting.
真恶心
And the note that went with itmade my teeth hurt, it was so saccharin.
还有那留言条 写的都酸死了 我牙都倒了
He used words like"soul mate" and "eternity."
说什么“心心相印的伴侣” 什么“永恒”
I almostpuked in the vase.
我差点吐出来
What'd susan thinkabout that?
那么susan怎么想的？
Well,she seemedto be really into it.
她似乎很喜欢
Mike!
Mike！
Oh,wait,stop! Go back!
等一下 回去！
Stop! Stop a second.
停下来 等一下
Hey!What are you doing here?
你来干吗？
I just,uh,wanted to wishyou luck before your surgery.
就是来祝你手术成功
Aw,that's so sweet.
谢谢
You came all the waydown here just for me.
你还专程来看我
Yep. That's why I came.
是的 我来就是为了这个
Oh,it meansa lot to me that you came.
你能来我很高兴
Well,you take care,susan.
你多保重 susan
Okay.
好的
Bye.
再见
You forgotto give her your flowers.
你忘了给她花了
Ah,it's no big deal.
没关系
Hi,susan.
你好 susan
How are those drugsworking for you?You feeling good?
麻醉药起作用了吗？你觉得如何？
Super-duper.How you feeling?
好的不能再好了 你呢？
Well,um,you know I want you to know,
我想让你知道
what I said the other day--
那天我说的那些话--
that corny stuff about meholding your heart in my hands--
说什么我要抓住你的心这类的酸话--
well,what I meantto say was,
我想说的是
my feelings for you--they keep growing,
我对你感情 日益见深
and,uh,I think--
我觉得--
well,I hope that you feel the same way about me.Mm.
呃 我希望你对我的感觉也是如此
Ah,hell,susan.
啊 susan
I love you.
我爱你
Aw,thank you.
哦 谢谢
I love mike.
我爱mike
Mike?
Mike？
Susan,who's mike?
Susan 谁是mike？
Mike is love. Mmm.
Mike是我的真爱
Who the hell is mike?
谁是mike?
I don't know,but she's marriedto a guy named karl.
我不知道 不过她嫁给了一个叫karl的男人
I'm so,so sorry.I should've told you,dr. Ron.
我很抱歉 我应该早点告诉你的 Ron医师
Mmm,mike,mike,mike...
oh,why are you alwaysfalling in love with skanks?
哦 你为何总爱上那些水性杨花的女人？
You beautiful,beautiful man!
你是个多出色英俊的男人啊
Oh!
哦!
okay,we ready to go here?
准备好了吗？
Yeah. Sure.
是的
Let's cutthis bitch open.
就让我们开了这个婊子吧
what are you doing?
你在干吗？
Your lawyer left a messageon my machine.
你的律师电话留言了
It seems we havea hearing in four weeks,
四周后要举行听证会
and I wanna be ready.
我要做好准备
Oh,I get it.
哦 我明白了
So,uh,so you're gonna pretendto be sober for the judge?
你要在法官面前假装没醉酒
Oh,there's no pretending.
不是假装
I am going to my first A.A. Meeting tomorrow.
我明天要参加嗜酒者互诫协会的见面会
Of course,I picked onein the worst part of town
当然了 我故意挑了一个别的地方的伙伴
so I won'trun into anybody I know.
这样我就不会遇到熟人
Which,of course,means I will.
其实还是会遇到
All right,so whatis that gonna prove?
好吧 这又能说明什么？
Perception is reality,andrew.
公众观念是很重要的 andrew
And if people perceive meto have a drinking problem,
如果大家认为我有酗酒恶习
then I do.
我就有了
And I certainly don't wantsome idiotic judge
我当然不会让某个傻瓜法官
using my hobby as an excuseto make you rich.
以我的喜好为由让你暴富起来
So I'm simplygoing to give up my wine
所以我干脆就戒酒
and becomea recovering alcoholic.
成为一个改过的新人
Good plan,but it'll never work.
办法倒是不错 不过就是行不通
See,I'll bet you stillend up coming to court hammered.
我敢打赌你到法庭上时还是醉醺醺的
oh,andrew,you don't thinkI love you enough to
哦 andrew 你觉得我不爱你
give up alcohol?
所以不会戒酒？
Look,I'm 17,all right?
我已经17岁了
So you can only keep me herefor another year.
你最多还能困住我一年
Why notjust let me go?
为什么不肯放手？
Because I'm notdone with you yet.
因为我的职责还没完成
It's my job to teach you,
我的职责是教育你成人
and you are not half the manI know you can be.
可你现在还远没有成人
Yeah,well,I got news for you--
呃 我就这么跟你说吧-
this is as goodas I'm gonna get.
我绝不会罢手的
If I really thought that,
我要是这么想
I'd get a gun right nowand kill us both.
我肯定会掏出一把枪 杀了我们俩
Mom,we're both so unhappy.
妈妈 我们俩现在都不开心
Why not justlet me take my trust fund,
干吗不把钱给我
and I'll getout of your hair forever?
这样我就可以永远不烦你了？
Please.
求你了
You're a stone cold bitch,you know that?
你是个冷血的婊子 你知道不？
I'm sorry.I didn't quite catch that.
不好意思 你刚才说什么 我没听清楚
I hate you.
我恨你
You know,the oppositeof love isn't hate.
爱的对立面并非恨
It's indifference.
而是冷漠
And if you hate me,
如果你恨我
that means you still care,
就说明你还在乎我
and we're still connected,
我们之间还有亲情
and I still have a chanceto set you right.
我还有机会让你改邪归正
This is how bree van de kamp
这就是bree van de kamp
finally came to change her weekly routine.
如何最终改变了自己的每周安排
She still cleaned on tuesdays...
仍是周二打扫...
paid her bills on wednesdays...
周三交费...
and did her laundry on thursdays.
周四洗衣服
But her fridays
但每周的星期五
were now reserved for a meeting...
要参加一个会议...
a special meeting
一个特别的会议
where she stood in front of people she didn't know...
站在一大群素不相识的人前...
my name is bree,
我的名字是bree
and I am an alcoholic.
我是一名酗酒者
And said things she didn't believe.
违心地诉说着
And afterwards,bree would come home
而后 回到家中
and reward herself...
犒劳自己...
on the completion of another successful week.
祝贺完满成功的一周